elbow_and_forearm_oian_quiz = [
    {"question": "What is the origin of Biceps Brachii?", "options": ["Supraglenoid tubercle of scapula", "Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Olecranon process of ulna"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Biceps Brachii?", "options": ["Coronoid process of ulna", "Radial tuberosity", "Distal phalanges of fingers"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Biceps Brachii?", "options": ["Pronates forearm", "Extends elbow", "Flexes elbow and supinates forearm"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Biceps Brachii?", "options": ["Radial nerve", "Musculocutaneous nerve", "Median nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Triceps Brachii?", "options": ["Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Infraglenoid tubercle of scapula", "Lateral epicondyle of humerus"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Triceps Brachii?", "options": ["Radial tuberosity", "Olecranon process of ulna", "Coronoid process of ulna"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Triceps Brachii?", "options": ["Supinates forearm", "Extends elbow", "Flexes elbow"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Triceps Brachii?", "options": ["Radial nerve", "Musculocutaneous nerve", "Median nerve"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Brachialis?", "options": ["Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Lateral epicondyle of humerus", "Distal half of anterior humerus"], "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Brachialis?", "options": ["Radial tuberosity", "Ulnar tuberosity and coronoid process", "Olecranon process of ulna"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Brachialis?", "options": ["Supinates forearm", "Flexes elbow", "Extends elbow"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Brachialis?", "options": ["Radial nerve", "Musculocutaneous nerve", "Median nerve"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the origin of Brachioradialis?", "options": ["Lateral supracondylar ridge of humerus", "Medial epicondyle of humerus", "Distal half of anterior humerus"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the insertion of Brachioradialis?", "options": ["Radial tuberosity", "Radial styloid process", "Ulnar tuberosity"], "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What is the action of Brachioradialis?", "options": ["Flexes forearm", "Pronates forearm", "Extends elbow"], "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "What is the nerve of Brachioradialis?", "options": ["Radial nerve", "Musculocutaneous nerve", "Median nerve"], "answer": "a"}
]
